scriptplazza.com 2011-05-30

# Privacy Policy — ScriptPlazza

USERS’ PRIVACY IS VERY IMPORTANT TO SCRIPTPLAZZA AND WE HAVE ADOPTED THIS PRIVACY POLICY AS IT RECOGNISES THE RIGHTS OF VISITORS TO OUR SITE TO KEEP THEIR PERSONAL INFORMATION PRIVATE.

1\. PRIVACY. ScriptPlazza is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of visitors to our web sites as well as the privacy of our actual customers, affiliates, subscribers and registered resellers. For visitors, we’ve structured our web sites so that, in general, you can visit us on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. For customers, affiliates, subscribers and registered resellers, once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with ScriptPlazza. 

2\. WHAT INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT. ScriptPlazza may collect personally identifiable information from users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where users are invited to volunteer such information. We collect your name, email address and website. Under no circumstances will we use this information for anything else not described in this privacy notice.

3\. HOW WE USE INFORMATION. ScriptPlazza may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by ScriptPlazza and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with ScriptPlazza and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners.

4\. MAINTENANCE OF INFORMATION. Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

5\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY. From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our customers will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others.
